[{
        "question": "What was the strange food combination eaten by the 11th doctor ate after his regeneration?",
        "choice1": "Prawns and banana",
        "choice2": "Fish fingers and custard",
        "choice3": "Tuna and avocado",
        "choice4": "Salmon and cream",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "What drink revived the 10th doctor after regenerating?",
        "choice1": "Tea",
        "choice2": "Coffee",
        "choice3": "Gin",
        "choice4": "Hot chocolate",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which doctor's first sentence was 'Half an hour ago I was a white haired scotsman!'",
        "choice1": "10",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "13",
        "choice4": "5",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which doctor loved jelly babies",
        "choice1": "4",
        "choice2": "12",
        "choice3": "7",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How many regenerations of the doctor appeared in the 50th anniversary episode 'The Day of The Doctor'?",
        "choice1": "13",
        "choice2": "12",
        "choice3": "3",
        "choice4": "8",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What doctor encountered the TARDIS as a human",
        "choice1": "10",
        "choice2": "7",
        "choice3": "5",
        "choice4": "11",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What colour were the sixth doctor's shoes?",
        "choice1": "red",
        "choice2": "blue",
        "choice3": "green",
        "choice4": "yellow",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which doctor visited his own tomb?",
        "choice1": "11",
        "choice2": "3",
        "choice3": "7",
        "choice4": "10",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What alias does the doctor often use on Earth when posing as a human?",
        "choice1": "John Smith",
        "choice2": "John White",
        "choice3": "John Miller",
        "choice4": "John Brown",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What actor played the Seventh Doctor?",
        "choice1": "David Tennant",
        "choice2": "Sylvester McCoy",
        "choice3": "Paul McGann",
        "choice4": "Christopher Eccleston",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What Planet does the doctor come from?",
        "choice1": "Earth",
        "choice2": "Tatooine",
        "choice3": "Skaro",
        "choice4": "Gallifrey",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the doctor's most important tool?",
        "choice1": "Sonic Screwdriver",
        "choice2": "Laser Spanner",
        "choice3": "Sonic Pliers",
        "choice4": "Laser Hammer",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which actor played the first doctor?",
        "choice1": "Jon Pertwee",
        "choice2": "Patrick Troughton",
        "choice3": "Matt Smith",
        "choice4": "William Hartnell",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Which doctor carries arround a spare hand in a jar?",
        "choice1": "13th",
        "choice2": "5th",
        "choice3": "10th",
        "choice4": "2nd",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the episode in which the first doctor regenerates?",
        "choice1": "The Tenth Moon",
        "choice2": "The Tenth Day",
        "choice3": "The Tenth Planet",
        "choice4": "The Tenth Moment",
        "answer": 3
    }
]